A Guide to the 1930-1999
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Alphabetical Files 1935-1994
  - Virginia Union University, Bryan Learning Resources Center 1988-1989 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Union University, Development Committee, n.d. 1992-1993 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Union University, Finances 1984, 1986-1989, 1991-1992 (Box 102)
  - VUU-Pledge 1988 (Box 102)
  - Adolescent Health Program 1993 (Box 103)
  - AIDS (Its no illusion) 1993-1994 (Box 103)
  - American Red Cross Advisory Committee 1991-1994 (Box 103)
  - Arts Council of Richmond, inc 1988 (Box 103)
  - Arts Council Strategic Overview 1995 (Box 103)
  - Ashe, Arthur Memorial Statue 1993-1996 (Box 103)
  - Aspen Institute 1988-1989 (Box 103)
  - Aspen Institute, n.d. 1988, 1990-1992 (Box 103)
  - Aspen Inst. Associates, n.d. 1992 (Box 103)
  - Aspen Institute 1992 (Box 103)
  - Aspen Institute 1993 (Box 103)
  - Aspen Institute 1993-1995 (Box 103)
  - Aspen Institute 1996-1998 (Box 103)
  - Aspen Institute 1995 (Box 103)
  - Association for the Preservation of Civil War Sites 1993-1995 (Box 103)
  - APVA 1987-1998 (Box 103)
  - Audubon Society 1990-1991 (Box 103)
  - Barksdale Theatre 1987-1988 (Box 103)
  - Battle Abbey Council, n.d. 1984, 1985 (Box 103)
  - Beacon Hill, n.d. (Box 103)
  - Billboards, n.d. 1983, 1986-1990 (Box 103)
  - Billboards 1993 (Box 103)
  - Black History Museum, Board of Trustees 1994, 1996 (Box 103)
  - Black History Museum Board, n.d. 1997-1998 (Box 103)
  - Boston Life, n.d. 1993 (Box 103)
  - Brain and Gifted Children, n.d. (Box 103)
  - Broad Street Association 1988-1990 (Box 103)
  - Cabell, James Branch Library Associates 1988-1995 (Box 104)
  - CAFF 1995-1996 (Box 104)
  - CAFF 1996-1997 (Box 104)
  - CAFF-Religious Freedom Day 1994-1995 (Box 104)
  - Canal 1989-1990 (Box 104)
  - Carver, J. Hampton, III 1991 (Box 104)
  - Cancer Ball October 20, 1989 (Box 104)
  - Canterbury Cathedral 1991-1992 (Box 104)
  - Caucus for the Future of Central Virginia 1992-1996 (Box 104)
  - CC-M Productions, Robert Mason 1982-1984 (Box 104)
  - Cheekwood Book, n.d. 1981, 1989 (Box 104)
  - Children's Festival 1988 (Box 104)
  - Center for the Study of Great Ideas 1996 (Box 104)
  - Central Va. Public Broadcasting (Box 104)
  - Central Richmond Association 1992 (Box 104)
  - Christian Children's Fund Advisory Committee 1992-1995 (Box 104)
  - Church Schools in the Diocese of Virginia 1981-1988 (Box 104)
  - Cities in School, n.d. 1991-1992 (Box 104)
  - Class Mother-7th Grade 1961-1962 (Box 104)
  - Colonial Dames 1990-1994 (Box 104)
  - Collector's Circle 1982-1994 (Box 104)
  - Commission for the Preservation of the Capital, n.d. (Box 104)
  - Commission for the Preservation of the Capitol, n.d. 1990-1992, 1994 (Box 104)
  - Committee to Honor Lucille Murray Brown 6/30/95 (Box 104)
  - Commonwealth Girl Scout Council-Keynote Address 16 April 1994 (Box 104)
  - Conserve Virginia, n.d. 1992-1996 (Box 104)
  - Cultural Decline 1994 (Box 104)
  - DE Tocqueville Society 1987-1994 (Box 104)
  - DE Tocqueville Society 1995-1997 (Box 104)
  - Disney, Newspaper Clipping 1/16/95 (Box 104)
  - Driver Improvement Program, n.d. (Box 104)
  - Democracy Television Series, n.d. 1982-1984 (Box 104)
  - Downtown Richmond, Inc., n.d. 1991-1992 (Box 104)
  - DuPont Award Luncheon May 22, 1997 (Box 104)
  - Economic/Commerce Consortum-Human Relations Study 1991 (Box 105)
  - Ellen Glasgow Festival 1992-1993 (Box 105)
  - Enterprise Development Company, n.d. 1984-1987 (Box 105)
  - Entertainment Committee-Museum, n.d. 1977-1989 (Box 105)
  - Entertainment Committee-VMFA 1991 (Box 105)
  - Faberye Ball 1996 (Box 105)
  - Faberye Ball and Dinner 1995 (Box 105)
  - Family and Children's Trust Fund, n.d. 1994 (Box 105)
  - First Freedom Award 1995-1996 (Box 105)
  - Flag Richmond, n.d. 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Fortune 500 1993 (Box 105)
  - Freedom House, n.d. 1992 (Box 105)
  - D.S. Freeman, Biography Correspondence (Charles L Wentworth, Photo Editor) 1983 (Box 105)
  - Friends of Winterhur 1993-1994 (Box 105)
  - Fund Raising 1990 (Box 105)
  - Genes, PBS Series, n.d. (Box 105)
  - Gettysburg (Newspaper Clippings) January 14, 1994 (Box 105)
  - Girl Scouts 1989-1997 (Box 105)
  - Governor's Alliance for a Drug Free Virginia Foundation, n.d. 1992-1993 (Box 105)
  - Governor's Commission of Excellence, n.d. 1989-1990 (Box 105)
  - Governor's Mansion 175th Anniv. Committee, n.d. 1987-1988 (Box 105)
  - Greater Richmond Community Foundation 1988 (Box 105)
  - Gun Control-League of Women Voters, n.d. 1990-1991 (Box 105)
  - Gun Control-League of Women Voters, n.d. 1992-1993 (Box 105)
  - Hawk Press-Richard Walker 1986 (Box 105)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation, n.d. 1987-1990 (Box 105)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation 1997-1998 (Box 105)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation 1990-1996 (Box 105)
  - History of Skylark Farm 1967, 1977 (Box 105)
  - H.O.M.E. 20th Anniversary Celebration 20 Sept. 1992 (Box 105)
  - Home Base 1982-1984 (Box 105)
  - Housing Opportunities made Equal, n.d. 1982-1983, 1985-1987 (Box 105)
  - Iraq-Save the children of 1993 (Box 105)
  - Junior Achievement 1992-1993 (Box 105)
  - Land Use Conference, n.d. (Box 105)
  - Lawn equipment and repairs 1990 (Box 105)
  - Lawn Society-LVA, n.d. 1984 (Box 105)
  - Lawson, Kay, Graduate School, n.d. 1961, 1989 (Box 105)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond May 7, 1992 (Box 105)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond June 2-3, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Lee Film Series, n.d. (Box 105)
  - Libby Prison Rededication Committee Sept. 18, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Library of Virginia 1995-1996 (Box 105)
  - Library of Virginia, Center for the Book, thru 1997 (Box 105)
  - Louisiana State University Press 1993 (Box 105)
  - Main Street Station, n.d. 1981-1982, 1984-1986, 1988 (Box 106)
  - George C. Marshall Research Foundation 1981, 1985 (Box 106)
  - Metropolitan Richmond Chamber of Commerce, n.d. (Speech?) (Box 106)
  - Metropolitan Richmond Convention and Visitor's Bureau 1986-1988 (Box 106)
  - Monument Commission City of Richmond 1991 (Box 106)
  - Monumental Church 1974, 1984 (Box 106)
  - Monumental Church, n.d. (Box 106)
  - Moral-Re-armament 1991 (Box 106)
  - MS Hope Award 1996 (Box 106)
  - Multiple Sclerosis, n.d. 1994 (Box 106)
  - Museum Fund Drive 1981 (Box 106)
  - National Anthem 1985-1986 (Box 106)
  - National Geographic, n.d. 1977, 1979 (Box 106)
  - National Society to Prevent Blindness 1992-1994 (Box 106)
  - National Symphony, n.d. 1981-1982 (Box 106)
  - New Virginia Review 1991-1997 (Box 106)
  - Nutrition, Sept. 1993 (Box 106)
  - Outlands 1990 (Box 106)
  - Order of St. John 1997-1998 (Box 106)
  - Order of St. John 1994-1996 (Box 106)
  - Order of the Hospital of St. John, n.d. 1991-1994 (Box 106)
  - Organ Committee-St. Pauls, n.d. 1987-1990 (Box 106)
  - Paideia Progress 1992 (Box 106)
  - Pastoral Counseling Publications, n.d. (Box 106)
  - Petersburg National Battlefield, n.d. 1989 (Box 106)
  - BK-Phi Beta Kappa Talk, n.d. March 26, 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 106)
  - Planned Parenthood, n.d. 1988-1990 (Box 106)
  - Planned Parenthood, n.d. 1993-1994 (Box 106)
  - Planned Parenthood, n.d. 1991, 1994-1996 (Box 106)
  - Police Community Banquet 1992-1994 (Box 106)
  - Politics 1990-1992, 1994 (Box 106)
  - Poplar Forest, Meeting January 14, 1992 (Box 106)
  - Powhatan Historical Society 1994 (Box 106)
  - Preservation Alliance of Virginia, n.d. 1992-1993 (Box 106)
  - Preservation Alliance of Virginia 1994-1997 (Box 106)
  - Project Discover, n.d. 1987-1988 (Box 106)
  - RR? Racism, n.d. 1991-1993 (Box 107)
  - Racism, n.d. 1992-1994 (Box 107)
  - Randon 1989 (Box 107)
  - Rappahannock Community College, n.d. 1983 (Box 107)
  - Raspberry, Bill, Speech April 21, 1993 (Box 107)
  - Ratification Minutes 1988 (Box 107)
  - Reading Group, n.d. 1983 (Box 107)
  - Recipe 1986-1991 (Box 107)
  - Recordings for the Blind 1994 (Box 107)
  - Recycling Association of Central VA 1992-1996 (Box 107)
  - Red Cross, n.d. 1991-1992 (Box 107)
  - Richmond Ballet-Correspondence Netes, Minutes, Repents 1997-1998 (Box 107)
  - Richmond Business Council 1993-1995 (Box 107)
  - Richmond First Club, n.d. 1992-1993, 1996-1998 (Box 107)
  - Richmond Hill, n.d. 1989-1993 (Box 107)
  - Richmond One to One Leadership Council, n.d. 1992-1997 (Box 107)
  - Richmond Peace Education Center 1989-1992 (Box 107)
  - Richmond Public Schools Review Committee, n.d. 1989-1992 (Box 107)
  - Richmond Urban League, n.d. 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 107)
  - Royal Horticultural Society, n.d. (Box 107)
  - Richmond Symphony 1985-1996 (Box 107)
  - Richmond Symphony Council 1995-1998 (Box 107)
  - Richmond Urban Institute, n.d. 1986 (Box 107)
  - Robert E. Lee, Speech, n.d. 1985 (Box 107)
  - Route 5 Plantations 1988 (Box 107)
  - St. Paul's College Party n.d. 1993-1994 (Box 107)
  - Shockoe Bottom, n.d. 1983-1984 (Box 107)
  - Richmond Ballet 1986-1997 (Box 107)
  - Society of Architectural Historians 1995 (Box 107)
  - Southern Environmental Law Center 1997 (Box 107)
  - Southern Environmental Law Center 1986-1996 (Box 107)
  - Southern Women's Show, n.d. April 30, May 3, 1992, 1991-1994 (Box 107)
  - Style Magazine 1985-1992 (Box 107)
  - Task Force for Historic Preservation and the Minority Community, Inc, n.d. 1988-1992 (Box 108)
  - Theatre Virginia 1989-1996 (Box 108)
  - Time 1989 (Box 108)
  - Transitional Housing for Battered Women and their children 1992 (Box 108)
  - Theatre Virginia-New Stages/New Writers, n.d. 1990-1992 (Box 108)
  - Tradescant Gardeners of America 1990 (Box 108)
  - Trees for Richmond Correspondence 1969, 1986, 1990-1993, 1997 (Box 108)
  - Trinity Church Boston 1967-1989 (Box 108)
  - United Negro College Fund/Flame Bearer Education Award 1995 (Box 108)
  - Valentine Museum 1982-1992 (Box 108)
  - Violence Prevention Project 1992-1993 (Box 108)
  - Va. Assn of Fund Raising Executives, n.d. 1990 (Box 108)
  - Virginia Business Council 1993 (Box 108)
  - Virginia Center for Public Press, n.d. 1991-1992 (Box 108)
  - VCU, n.d. 1990-1993 (Box 108)
  - VCU Honorary Degree, SAT 10 a.m. May 22, 1993 (Box 108)
  - VCU Jacob House 1995 (Box 108)
  - VCU Talk Toward A mor Livable City (Fondroff) 1991 (Box 108)
  - Virginia Council of Churches 1992-1994 (Box 108)
  - Virginia Enviromental Endowment, n.d. (Box 108)
  - VA Enviromental Endowment, n.d. 1990 (Box 108)
  - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities December 1988-December 1996 (Box 108)
  - Virginia Heros 1992-1996 (Box 108)
  - Council of the Virginia Museum 1984-1997 (Box 108)
  - Fellow-VA Museum 1977-1997 (Box 108)
  - Virginia Technology Research Park 1992-1994 (Box 108)
  - VA Womens Hall of Fame, n.d. 1989, 1991-1993 (Box 108)
  - WCVE Program Outspoker! Black and White in Richmond 1996-1997 (Box 108)
  - Woman's Club, n.d. 1981-1996, 1996, 1982-1996 (Box 108)
  - Women's Health Conference May 19-20, 1995 (Box 108)
  - Women's Issues, n.d. 1985 (Box 108)
  - Women's Yellow Pages 1990-1992 (Box 108)
  - Workship Board, n.d. 1981-1983, 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 108)
  - YMCA 1990-1994 (Box 109)
  - YMCA-OWA 11/06/96 (Box 109)
  - YMCA-Advisory Board, n.d. 1993-1996 (Box 109)
  - YMCA-OWA Alumni Reception 1995-1996 (Box 109)
  - YMCA Advisory 1997-1999 (Box 109)
  - YMCA-OWA 1996-1997 (Box 109)
  - "64" Magazine - Lorna Wyckoff n.d., 1999-2001 (Box 110)
  - "64" Magazine, n.d., 2001-2002 (Box 110)
  - Acorn Club, n.d., 1993-2001 (Box 110)
  - Adler, Mortimer and Caroline, n.d., 1988, 1992, 1994 (Box 110)
  - Adler, Mortimer, n.d., 2001 (Box 110)
  - African American Sports Hall of Fame, n.d., 1997 (Box 110)
  - After-Death Experiences, n.d., 1976-1977 (Box 110)
  - Advocacy Committee (public policy), 1992 (Box 110)
  - Alliance Francaise, n.d., 1991-1992 (Box 110)
  - America's Promise, n.d., 1997-2000 (Box 110)
  - American Image Marketing (AIM), 1995 (Box 110)
  - American Institute of Architects (AIA), n.d., 1991-1999 (Box 110)
  - Appeal Letter (Annual Fund) n.d., 1991-1995 (Box 110)
  - Architectural Literacy - C. Loth, n.d., 2001 (Box 110)
  - Arkin, Daniel, n.d., 1991 (Box 110)
  - Aspen, n.d., 1998, 1999 (Box 110)
  - Baliles, Gerald L. (former Governor of Virginia) and Jeannie, n.d., 1984-1989 (Box 110)
  - Baltimore, n.d., 1986 (Box 110)
  - Bathroom Carpets - 1996 (Box 110)
  - Battlefields, n.d., 1995 (Box 110)
  - Better Housing Coalition, Board of Directors, n.d., 1999-2000 (1 of 2) (Box 110)
  - Better Housing Coalition, Board of Directors, n.d., 1999-2000 (2 of 2) (Box 110)
  - Better Housing Coalition, Board Meetings - 2000, n.d., 2000-20001 (Box 110)
  - Billboards, n.d., 1997-1999 (Box 110)
  - Black History Museum Board, n.d., 1999-2003 (Box 110)
  - Blackwell - Hope VI, n.d., 1997-1998 (Box 110)
  - Body Strider, n.d. (Box 110)
  - Book Club - Richmond, n.d., 1972, 1994-1995, 1996, 1997-1998 (Box 110)
  - Brooklyn Botanic Garden, n.d., 1977-1980, 1991-1999 (Box 110)
  - Brown J. Carter, n.d., 2001-2002 (Box 110)
  - Bush, n.d., 2001 (Box 110)
  - Cabell, James Branch Library Associates, n.d., 1996-2001 (Box 110)
  - Capital One Services, Inc., n.d. (Box 110)
  - Capitol Square commission, n.d., 1997-1999 (Box 110)
  - Carpenter, June, n.d., 1996 (Box 110)
  - Carpenter Center, n.d., 1998 (Box 110)
  - Cary News-Cary Street 2000 (Box 110)
  - Chamber of Commerce, n.d., 1999-2002 (Box 110)
  - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, n.d., 1998-2000 (Box 110)
  - Church Hill Neighborhood, Inc., n.d., 1988-2001 (Box 110)
  - Circuit City Foundation, n.d., 1995 (Box 110)
  - Cities in Schools, n.d., 1995 (Box 110)
  - City Council Richmond Better Housing Coalition (RBHC), n.d., 1990-1992 (Box 110)
  - City Slickers, n.d., 1999 (Box 110)
  - Cleary, Ben- University of Richmond Ryland Hall, Tuesday October 5, 1999 8:45 am Room 212 (Box 110)
  - Clement, Whitt for Attorney General, n.d., 2001 (Box 110)
  - Clinic?, n.d., 1999, 2001 (Box 110)
  - Coalition for a Greater Richmond, 1996-1999 (Box 110)
  - College Admissions Recommendations, n.d., 1988-1996 (Box 110)
  - College of Physicians (JLM), n.d., 2000 (Box 110)
  - Columns on Grove, n.d., 1996-2001 (Box 110)
  - Commonwealth Girl Scout Council, n.d., 1998-2002 (Box 110)
  - Communities in Schools, n.d., 1997-1999 (Box 110)
  - The Community Foundation, n.d., 1988-2001 (Box 111)
  - Conserve Virginia, n.d., 1995-1999 (Box 111)
  - Costs- Projects and Office, n.d., 1995 (Box 111)
  - Council for America's First Freedom, n.d., 1998-1999 (Box 111)
  - Council for America's First Freedom, n.d., 1998-2000 (Box 111)
  - Council for America's First Freedom, n.d./ 1999-2002 (Box 111)
  - Council for America's First Freedom (CAFF) - Queen Noor and First Freedom Awards, 1/16/01, n.d. 2000 (Box 111)
  - Covington Travel, n.d.,1998 (Box 111)
  - Cowling, Dr. Dorothy N., n.d., 2000 (Box 111)
  - Crestar Bank, n.d., 1990-1994 (Box 111)
  - Crowley, Sheila, n.d., 1995, 1997 (Box 111)
  - De Tocqueville Society, n.d., 1998-2002 (Box 111)
  - Dickon, Chris, WHR Norfolk, n.d., 1997-1999 (Box 111)
  - Dombalis, Father Constantine N., Dean, Greek Orthodox Cathedral of Saints Constantine and Helen, n.d., 1983, 1988, 1989, 1995, 1997 (Box 111)
  - Dominion Resources, n.d., 2001 (Box 111)
  - Douglas S. Freeman High School, n.d., 1997-1999 (Box 111)
  - Douglas S. Freeman High School, n.d., 2000-2002 (Box 111)
  - Du Pont Grant- Diocese of Virginia, 1994 (Box 111)
  - Executive Committee- n.d., 1990-1998 (1of 2) (Box 111)
  - Executive Committee - n.d.,1990-1998 (2 of 2) (Box 111)
  - Fan Free Clinic, n.d., 1998-1999 (Box 111)
  - Federal Reserve Bank, n.d., 1994-1998 (Box 111)
  - Financial reports, n.d., 1996, 1997-2000 (Box 111)
  - First Presbyterian Church Adult S.S. Class, n.d., 2002 (Box 111)
  - Fogelson, Aliza, n.d., 1996 (Box 111)
  - Ford Foundation Proposal, n.d., 1988, 1994 (Box 111)
  - Foster, Dr. Francis and Carmen, n.d., 1989-1993 (Box 111)
  - Foundation for Advanced Study and Training (F.A.S.T.) 1998-2002 (1 of 3) (Box 111)
  - Foundations, n.d., 1990-1994 (2 of 3) (Box 111)
  - Foundations of Leadership Studies, Leadership in Formal Organization, History and Theories of Leadership, Leadership in Formal Organizations, Leadership In Political Systems, Leadership and Social Movements, Ethics and Leadership, Leadership in Community and Volunteer Organizations Decision Making (3 of 3) n.d.? (Box 111)
  - Framme, Lawrence H., 1995 (Box 111)
  - Galanti, Paul and Phyllis, 1998 (Box 111)
  - Gallagher, Dr. Gary, n.d., 1986-1998 (Box 111)
  - Garden Club of Virginia Historic Garden Week, Tuesday, April 20, 1999, n.d.1998-1999 (Box 111)
  - Governor's Community Service and Volunteerism Awards Program, n.d., 1995-1997 (Box 111)
  - Gray, MIM Richmond, n.d.,1988 (Box 111)
  - Grounds Upkeep - Bartlett Tree, etc. n.d. (Box 111)
  - Guns and Butter - NYT, Manchester Guardian, Thursday, September 27, n.d., 2001 (Box 111)
  - Hall, Frank Party 1/2/02 (Box 112)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation, n.d., 1998-2000 (Box 112)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation, n.d., 1999-2000 (Box 112)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation, n.d., 2001 (Box 112)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation, n.d., 2001- 2002 (Box 112)
  - Historic Richmond Party, n.d., November 11, 1999 (Box 112)
  - Hollins College, n.d., 1993 - 2002 (Box 112)
  - Hopkins, Evans, n.d., 1989-1998 (Box 112)
  - Houghton, Nina R., n.d., 1997 (Box 112)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), n.d., 1989-1996 (Box 112)
  - Inform, n.d., 1998-1999 (Box 112)
  - Interesting Articles, n.d., 1951, 1976, 1978, 1981, 1992-1996 (Box 112)
  - International Hospital for Children, n.d., 1999 (Box 112)
  - Jepson School, n.d., 1996-2002 (Box 112)
  - Jepson School Assessment Retreat, n.d., 1994 (Box 112)
  - Jepson School of Leadership Studies, n.d., 1987-1994 (Box 112)
  - Jepson School of Leadership Studies, 1997 (Box 112)
  - Journey into Science, n.d., 1996 (Box 112)
  - Junior League, n.d., 1994-2002 (Box 112)
  - Junior League of Richmond, n.d., 1997, 2001-2002 (Box 112)
  - Landmark Theatre, n.d., 1995-1996 (Box 112)
  - Lapham, Julie A., n.d., 1996-1997 (Box 113)
  - Leadership & Motivation, Understanding & Leading Individuals Service Learning, Internship Seminar, Historical Perspectives on Leadership The Leader as a Change Agent, Problems, Policy and Leadership, Senior Seminar, 1993-1994 (Box 113)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond, n.d., 1996, 2000-2001 (Box 113)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond (LMR) Bell Atlantic Conference, n.d., 1998-1999 (Box 113)
  - League of Women Voters, n.d., 1990-1999 (Box 113)
  - Lee Portrait-Canal Walk, n.d., 1999 (Box 113)
  - Legislature, n.d., 1993-2000 (Box 113)
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC) Advisory Committee 1997-2000 (1 of 2) (Box 113)
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC) Advisory Committee 1999-2000 (2 of 2) (Box 113)
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC) Advisory Committee Richmond (LISC) - Opening Doors, n.d., 1999 (Box 113)
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC) Link, 1996-2000 (Box 113)
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC) Richmond Neighborhood Development Fund, n.d., 1998 (Box 113)
  - Markham, Mrs. Sarah, n.d., 1995 (Box 113)
  - Mashoe, Mr. Marion, n.d., 1999 (Box 113)
  - aymont Foundation- 1998-1999 (Box 113)
  - Maymont Foundation - 2000-2002 (Box 113)
  - Maymont Nature Center, n.d., 1998-2001 (Box 113)
  - McCabe, Charles E., n.d., 1992-1993 (Box 113)
  - McCauley Institute Housing Gazette, 1999 (Box 113)
  - McClenahan Child Care Center, n.d., 1996-2000 (1 of 2) (Box 113)
  - McClenahan Child Care Center, n.d., 1997-1999 (2 of 2) (Box 113)
  - McClenney, Earl H., n.d., 1992 (Box 113)
  - McCoy, Sheila, n.d., 1994 (Box 113)
  - Mellon, Paul, September 17, 1997, n.d., 1997 (Box 113)
  - Metro Chamber, n.d., 1992-1998 (Box 113)
  - Middleditch, Leigh B., Jr., Experience: Sorensen Institute, n.d., 1997-1998 (Box 113)
  - Millenium, 2000 (Box 113)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d., 1992-1999 (Box 113)
  - Modlin Center Performances, n.d., 2002-2003 (Box 113)
  - Monticello Cabinet, n.d., 1997-2002 (Box 113)
  - Multiple Sclerosis, n.d., 1995-1997 (Box 113)
  - Multiple Sclerosis Award, n.d., 1994 (Box 113)
  - Museum of Scotland (includes photographs with the Queen of England), n.d., 1994-1999 (Box 113)
  - Music, n.d., 1996 (Box 113)
  - National Conference for Community & Justice (NCCJ), n.d., 1991-2001 (Box 114)
  - National Environmental Trust, 1997 (Box 114)
  - New Virginia Review, n.d., 1998-2001 (Box 114)
  - Nies-Berger, Edouard, n.d., 1992-1993, 1997 (Box 114)
  - Nominating Board Development Committee, n.d., 1997-2001 (1 of 2) (Box 114)
  - Nominating Board Development Committee, n.d., 1996-1997, 2002 (2 of 2) (Box 114)
  - Oliver, Chief Jerry, n.d., 2001 (Box 114)
  - Order of St. John, n.d., 1998-2000 (Box 114)
  - Order of St. John, n.d., 2000-2002 (Box 114)
  - Order of St. John, n.d., 2001 (Box 114)
  - Organized Executive, n.d., 1997-2000 (Box 114)
  - Partners Bridge Builder Award, n.d., 2001-2002 (Box 114)
  - Pasco, Robert Lancaster, n.d., 1997 (Box 114)
  - Philadelphia Museum, Joseph J. Rishel - Anne D'Arnoncourt, n.d., 1997 (Box 114)
  - Planned Parenthood, n.d., 1997-2001 (Box 114)
  - Political Scene, n.d., 1987-2002 (Box 114)
  - Powell, Justice Lewis Franklin, Jr., n.d., 1996-1999 (Box 114)
  - Quigg, Gerald, n.d., 1989-1999 (Box 114)
  - Richmond AIDS Ministry, n.d., 1997-1998 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Ballet, n.d, 1999 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Ballet Board, n.d., 1997-1999 (1 of 2) (Box 115)
  - Richmond Ballet Board, n.d., 1999 (2 of 2) (Box 115)
  - Richmond Ballet Board, n.d., 1999-2003 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Ballet Board, n.d., 2001-2002 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Ballet Board, n.d., 2001 - 2002 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Ballet - Minds in Motion, n.d., 1998, 2000 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Better Housing Coalition, n.d., 1993 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Better Housing Coalition, n.d., 1995 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Community High School, n.d., 1984 (Box 115)
  - Richmond First Club, 1998 - 2000 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Hill, n.d., 1996 - 2002 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Hill Leadership Council, n.d., 1999-2001 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Mercury, n.d., 1975 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Plans and Planners, n.d., 1999 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Public Library, n.d., 1996 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Renaissance, n.d., 1996-1998 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Renaissance, n.d., 1998-2000 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Renaissance, n.d., 2000 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Riverfront Development Corp., Richmond Historic Riverfront Foundation, n.d., 1999 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Symphony Council, n.d., 1999-2001 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Upon Thames Committee, Duke of Richmond, n.d., 2000 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Urban Forum, n.d., 1981, 1999-2001 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Urban Forum (RUF), n.d., 1990, 1993, 1996, 1998 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Urban Forum (RUF), n.d., 1997-1999 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Urban Forum, n.d., 1998-2000 (Box 115)
  - Richmond Urban Forum, n.d., 2000 (Box 115)
  - Robins, Claiborne & Lora, n.d., 1989-1995 (Box 115)
  - Sacred Heart Center, n.d., 1998 (Box 116)
  - Safe Landings, n.d., 1998 (Box 116)
  - Safes, n.d. (Box 116)
  - Sands, Courtenay, n.d., 1957, 1958, 1964, 1980, 1988, 1991, 1992, 1994, 1998, 1999 (Box 116)
  - Scenic America, n.d., 1994-1999 (Box 116)
  - Scenic Virginia, n.d., 1993, 1999-2001 (Box 116)
  - Scenic Virginia, n.d., 1998-1999 (1 of 2) (Box 116)
  - Scenic Virginia, n.d., 1998-1999 (2 of 2) (Box 116)
  - St. Catherine's, Mme. Sadat, n.d., 1992-1998 (Box 116)
  - St. Catherine's Reunion (17-18 April 1998), n.d., 1997-1998 (Box 116)
  - St. Paul's Arts Board, n.d., 1991-1998 (Box 116)
  - St. Paul's Church, n.d., 1994-1998 (Box 116)
  - St. Paul's Church, n.d., 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - St. Paul's Church, n.d., 2000 (Box 116)
  - St. Paul's Church, n.d., 2001-2002 (Box 116)
  - St. Paul's Church, n.d., 2002 (Box 116)
  - St. Paul's Church Endowment Fund, n.d., 1998-1999 (Box 116)
  - St. Paul's College, n.d., 1985-1995 (Box 116)
  - St. Paul's Forum, n.d., 1997-1998 (Box 116)
  - St. Paul's Vision Task Force, n.d. (Box 116)